<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Teng Jiang</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Teng Jiang</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 02:19:20 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Why Sebastian?</title>
      <link>/posts/why-sebastian/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 02:19:20 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/why-sebastian/</guid>
      <description>On social occasions, I go by Sebastian, a name I gave myself somehow arbitrarily when I was taking French in high school. I get a lot of &amp;ldquo;Oh, and it is &amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo; Of course, that&amp;rsquo;s not my given name. My given name is &amp;ldquo;Teng&amp;rdquo;(腾), which should be pronounced as [tʰəŋ], not [tʰɛn].
One of the reasons I chose Sebastian over Teng is the latter&amp;rsquo;s pronunciation: I genuinely do not want people to get confused.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to my World!</title>
      <link>/home/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 02:19:20 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/</guid>
      <description> See more of me from about, with selected projects, professional experiences and others. Contact me via LinkedIn or email me for my resume or opportunities.
News: 09/02/2022: I started my master&amp;rsquo;s degree at Columbia University as well as a new chapter of my life in NYC! 08/19/2022: I finished my internship at Tesla. 07/01/2022: I graduated Magna Cum Laude from Peking University. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>/about/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2023 00:10:31 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/about/</guid>
      <description>I usually go by Sebastian, a name not of my heritage but somehow I feel connected to (See Why Sebastian?).
My fields of interest encompass database systems, software engineering, high-performance computing, and time series analysis. I used to aim for a career as a quantitative developer but I took a sharp turn into Computer Science (See Detour to Quant), and I&amp;rsquo;m convinced that I&amp;rsquo;ve made the right decision.
I feel extremely privileged to be working with and constantly inspired by brilliant minds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Detour to Quant</title>
      <link>/posts/detour-to-quant/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 23:23:43 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/detour-to-quant/</guid>
      <description>I just think it would be nice to archive something I&amp;rsquo;ve done so that it would be lost.
I tutor prospective students enthusiastic about Financial Engineering at Peking University. Notes here. Deep-Deterministic-Policy-Gradient-based Dynamic Hedging Strategy: Repo under construction. </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
